

**Tomas Fiers** 

Signals, Software, and Science.

tomas.fiers@gmail.com 0032 478 13 43 26

## **Profile**

Inquisitive mind, architectural skills, and mindful of the other person's experience (user, client, colleague) • Proven quantitative skills, particularly in machine learning and data analysis • High signal-to-noise communication • Toolbox: applied mathematics, software engineering, and a broad background knowledge in tech & science

## **Experience**

NERF (imec - VIB - KU Leuven) – **Signal Processing Engineer in Neuroscience – Master's Thesis** 

FEBRUARI 2017 - PRESENT, LEUVEN

Fluves - Business Development Intern

SEPTEMBER 2017 - DECEMBER 2017, GHENT

Byteflies – Signal Processing Intern JULY 2017 – SEPTEMBER 2017, ANTWERP

Arenbergorkest – **President, Section Leader, Treasurer** 2013 – 2016, LEUVEN

DataCamp - Software Engineering Intern

JULY 2016 - SEPTEMBER 2016, LEUVEN

VVW & Sport Vlaanderen - Sailing Instructor

2010 - 2012, NIEUWPOORT, HEIST, HOFSTADE

## **Education**

KU Leuven – MSc, burgerlijk ingenieur – Biomedical Engineering 2016 – 2018

Electives in artificial intelligence & machine learning, advanced statistical methods for data-analysis, neuroscience, commercial law, and IT security.

**KU Leuven – BSc, Computer Science & Electrical Engineering** 2012 – 2016